Wha?... The entire weekend?
You mean I wouldn't see you at all?
But I do... No, no,
l knew what I was getting into.
(Penny:)You can't put a saddle
on Leonard Hofstadter.
(Penny:)Oh, my, is it getting hot in here? Ay, Papi.
"Ay, Papi"?
(Leonard:)- What is that?
- An acting choice.
(Stuart:)Hmm.
(Leonard:)So you chose that
when you become turned on...
...you'd turn into Speedy Gonzalez.
Do you got a problem with that, Papi?
(Leonard:)Uh-uh.
Penny? Penny? Penny?
(Penny:)Sorry, Stallion.
Your weird friend Giraffe is here.
(Sheldon:)Hello, Penny. I just stopped by
to bring you this gift.
Gummi Bears? Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Now that you're in my debt...
(Sheldon:)...please manipulate Amy into
releasing me from my commitment...